<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Full features document management software | FileHold]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Full features document management software | FileHold]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 21:31:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Document Management Software Saves Time and Money]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Document Management Software Saves Time and Money</h1><p>Paper and electronic information in the workplace grows daily at an uncontrollable speed. Keeping your intellectual property secure and in regulatory compliance is every organizations challenge. FileHold document management software converts paper and electronic information into a secure, organized, version controlled, searchable electronic library. The FileHold "paperless office" builds process efficiencies by allowing workers to collaborate and approve documents in electronic form.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2d0bb4c4dcd40546b3f97ecd0816357ab0437fc3.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/79876cb1-f7c7-47ba-986a-1babfe4b968f/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">79876cb1-f7c7-47ba-986a-1babfe4b968f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 21:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Document review and approval Anytime, Anywhere: Mobile FileHold]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Document review and approval Anytime, Anywhere: Mobile FileHold</h1><p>The reality of today’s business is that many key personnel spend a lot of time out of the office. The lack of immediate access to information can cause blocks in an organization's processes. With Mobile FileHold, documents are never out of reach. FileHold's mobile collaboration application is available for busy information workers who rely on their smart phones for productivity away from the office. Using HTML 5 technology, access secure content anytime, anywhere, from a mobile device.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/bfec8448ad48ac416e8f68404ee4cdeb85ea9586.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/3835e8ab-2983-4317-acf7-9caec2444c66/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3835e8ab-2983-4317-acf7-9caec2444c66</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 21:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Document Workflow and Approval Enables Collaboration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Document Workflow and Approval Enables Collaboration</h1><p>Most organizations deal with large volumes of paperwork every day which can become difficult to manage. This often leads to errors and loss of information that causes long delays and revisions. This inefficient use of time and employee resources results in a significant financial loss. Transition your team from slow, cumbersome, manual document processing to efficient document routing for review and approval. The FileHold workflow module, automates your business processes to increase productivity and decrease costs.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9e8fa3111b32171375c3d7440c262d23dd99c56f.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/2fa7a4c4-a2ce-41fa-99ae-e36924d4e0ec/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2fa7a4c4-a2ce-41fa-99ae-e36924d4e0ec</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 21:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Document Management Software System: FileHold]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Document Management Software System: FileHold</h1><p>Full-featured document management software from FileHold is feature rich, enterprise grade and affordable.  Its suite of features provide for document scanning, capture, indexing, storage, search, versioning, and document workflow review and approval. FileHold can be installed locally on your server for total security or in the cloud. Integrated with Microsoft office FileHold works on your desktop, browser, and mobile device. FileHold document management software makes it easy for organizations to improve security, increase compliance, streamline operations, and reduce  the use of paper while saving time and money. “Go paperless, go green” with FileHold document management software.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f7143bd100b60766d0ecc8d5a3300e23235144fb.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/filehold-systems-inc/document-management-software-system-filehold/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">50276e33-cd4e-4407-a56f-f7d5c7e69dce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 21:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>